Daniel Chavez

2047212248 dchavez3395@gmail.com Winnipeg, Manitoba

Summary

I'm a self-motivated Web Developer with years of experience with client work, and negotiating complex issues. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security. Organized approach to meeting multiple, concurrent deadlines. Pulls from active knowledge of current technology landscape to promote best practices in web design.

Experience

Birchwood Credit Solutions

Special Finance Manager, Winnipeg

11/2018 - 07/2021

- · Built strong client relationships and provided high value-adding services
- · Interviewed clients, verified Credit history and offered options based on their situation
- Wrote, negotiated and finalized Sales Contracts
- Emphasized product features based on customer's needs

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Business Development Manager, Brandon, Manitoba

01/2018 - 11/2018

- Coordinated innovative strategies to accomplish marketing objectives and boost long-term profitability.
- Developed and implemented favorable pricing structures balancing firm objectives against customer targets.
- Collected and responded to user feedback through iterative improvements to site structure and content.
- Planned and executed website editorial schedule by collaborating with designers, web developers, marketing and sales staff.
- Converted design assets into component-based HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Developed and implemented WordPress sites, themes and plugins.
- Referenced web analytics reporting to enhance designs and improve site performance.
- Collaborated with end users on project specifications, strategy and execution to build new WordPress pages and update existing ones.

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Sales Consultant, Brandon, Manitoba

05/2015 - 01/2018

- Bronze Nissan Club Excellence Winner for 2016
- Highest closing ratio in the store for 2016, 2018
- Identified and qualified client's needs, developed sales strategies and negotiated profitable projects with a high success rate
- Provided repeat clients with exceptional care and attention.

Skills

HTML5, CSS, SCSS (Sassy Cascading Style Sheets), Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, Responsive Web Design, Programming, CMS (Content Management System), WordPress

Education

High School

Languages

English, Spanish

References

Cierra Waddell-Hodgson

General Sales Manager

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Phone: 204-573-7460

email: cierra.waddell@hotmail.com

Brady Sobering

Sales Manager

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Phone: 204-612-2497

email: brady.sobering@gmail.com

Cory Creighton

Finance Manager

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Phone: 204-724-7225

email: corycreighton@hotmail.com